<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="53">
	<author>Jason06</author>
	<version>1.0.0.5</version>
    <title>
		<en>Extended Tabbing</en>
		<de>Erweitertes Tabbing</de>
		<fr>Tabbing Avancé</fr>
    </title>
    <description>
		<en>
<![CDATA[
"Tab" into nearest vehicles, or choose another target, all sorted by distance

Features:
- Shows the target before tab execution
- Possibility to change target before tabbing, vehicles are sorted by distance
- Tab key (Ctrl left + TAB): Activate the function, choose your target by pressing 'Ctrl left + Arrow left or right', press the tab-key again to enter target
- Quick-Tab key (Ctrl left + Shift left + TAB): Instantly tab into nearest vehicle, change target with arrow-keys while holding the keys down
- Save up to five vehicles for direct access (Alt left + 1, Alt left + 2, Alt left + 3, Alt left + 4, Alt left + 5)
- All key bindings can be changed
- Full multiplayer support

How it works:
- Activate ExtendedTabbing with Ctrl left + Tab
- Use Ctrl left with arrow left or right to choose a vehicle
- If you like, save the selected vehicle with Alt-1, Alt-2, Alt-3, Alt-4, or Alt-5 for direct access
- Press Ctrl left + Tab again to enter the selected vehicle
- QuickTab: Press Ctrl left + Shift left + Tab to enter the nearest vehicle immediately. Alter the target with Ctrl left + Arrow left or right before releasing the keys.

Changelog V1.0.1.0
- Vehicle-Slots increased from 3 to 5
- Reworked the default key bindings to resolve issues on windows pc
- Improved handling of player data while loading
]]>
		</en>	
		<de>
<![CDATA[
Schnelles "tabben" in das jeweils nächstgelegene Fahrzeug oder in alternative Ziele, sortiert nach Entfernung

Features:
- Anzeige des "Tab"-Ziels vor Ausführung
- Möglichkeit, das Ziel zu wechseln, die Reihenfolge entspricht der Entfernung von der aktuellen Position des Spielers
- Aktivieren/Auslösen-Taste (Strg links + TAB): Aktiviert die Funktion und zeigt das ausgewählte Fahrzeug an, das mit 'Strg links und Pfeil rechts / Pfeil links' geändert werden kann. Erneuter Tastendruck löst dann den Wechsel aus.
- QuickTab-Taste (Strg links + Shift links + TAB): Wechselt sofort zum nächstgelegenen Fahrzeug, bei gehaltenen Tasten kann auch hier das Ziel mit den Pfeiltasten geändert werden.
- Bis zu fünf Fahrzeuge können für den schnellen Direktzugriff gespeichert werden, anschließend kann direkt per Tastendruck hineingesprungen werden (Alt link + 1, Alt links + 2, Alt links + 3, Alt links + 4, Alt links + 5)
- Alle Tastenbelegungen können geändert werden
- Voller Multiplayer-Support

Funktionsweise:
- Aktiviere ExtendedTabbing mit Strg links + Tab
- Wähle mit Strg + Pfeil links oder Strg + Pfeil rechts das gewünschte Fahrzeug
- Speichere das ausgewählte Fahrzeug bei Bedarf mit Alt-1, Alt-2, Alt-3, Alt-4, oder Alt-5 für den Schnellzugriff
- Drücke erneut Strg links + Tab, um in das ausgewählte Fahrzeug zu springen
- QuickTab: Drücke Strg links + Shift links + Tab um direkt in das nächstgelegene Fahrzeug zu springen, halte die Tasten gedrückt, um mit Strg + Pfeiltasten ein anderes Fahrzeug auszuwählen

Changelog V1.0.1.0
- Speicherplätze für Fahrzeuge von 3 auf 5 erhöht
- Standard-Tastenbelegung überarbeitet, um Probleme auf Windows-PC zu beseitigen
- Ladevorgang der Spielerdaten verbessert
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
<![CDATA[
Accédez rapidement au véhicule le plus proche ou à d'autres destinations, triées par distance.

Caractéristiques :
- Affichage de la cible "tab" avant l'exécution.
- Possibilité de changer de cible, l'ordre correspondant à la distance de la position actuelle du joueur
- Touche d'activation/déclenchement (Ctrl gauche + TAB) : active la fonction et affiche le véhicule sélectionné, qui peut être modifié avec 'Ctrl gauche et flèche droite/flèche gauche'. Une nouvelle pression sur la touche déclenchera alors le changement.
- Touche QuickTab (Ctrl gauche + Shift gauche + TAB) : passe immédiatement au véhicule le plus proche, si les touches sont maintenues enfoncées, la destination peut également être modifiée ici avec les touches fléchées.
- Il est possible de mémoriser jusqu'à cinq véhicules pour un accès direct rapide, puis d'y accéder directement en appuyant sur une touche (Alt gauche + 1, Alt gauche + 2, Alt gauche + 3, Alt gauche + 4, Alt gauche + 5).
- Toutes les affectations de touches peuvent être modifiées
- Support multijoueur complet

Comment cela fonctionne :
- Activez la fonction ExtendedTabbing avec Ctrl gauche + Tab.
- Sélectionnez le véhicule souhaité avec Ctrl + Flèche gauche ou Ctrl + Flèche droite.
- Sauvegarder le véhicule sélectionné avec Alt-1, Alt-2, Alt-3, Alt-4 ou Alt-5 pour un accès rapide en cas de besoin.
- Appuyez à nouveau sur Ctrl gauche + Tab pour passer au véhicule sélectionné.
- QuickTab : Appuyez sur les touches Ctrl gauche + Shift gauche + Tab pour sauter directement dans le véhicule le plus proche, maintenez les touches enfoncées pour sélectionner un autre véhicule avec les touches Ctrl + Flèches.

Changelog V1.0.1.0
- Augmentation du nombre d'emplacements mémoire pour les véhicules de 3 à 5
- Révision du mappage des touches par défaut pour résoudre les problèmes sur les PC Windows
- Amélioration du chargement des données des joueurs
]]>
	</fr>
 	</description>	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<extraSourceFiles>
        <sourceFile filename="extendedTabbing.lua" />
    </extraSourceFiles>
	<actions>
		<action name="XTB_EXECTAB" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FASTTAB" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_TOGGLEHELP" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_PREV" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_NEXT" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FAV1" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FAV2" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FAV3" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FAV4" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
		<action name="XTB_FAV5" category="VEHICLE" ignoreComboMask="false" />
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>	
		<actionBinding action="XTB_EXECTAB">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_tab" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FASTTAB">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_lshift KEY_tab" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_TOGGLEHELP">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_rctrl KEY_tab" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_PREV">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_left" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_NEXT">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lctrl KEY_right" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FAV1">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_1" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FAV2">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_2" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FAV3">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_3" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FAV4">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_4" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="XTB_FAV5">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_lalt KEY_5" neutralInput="0" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
	<l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
</modDesc>
